双峰
第三季  第十五集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     吃冰棒   Silence   詹木头
翻译     一只虾  TheWalkingNerd  酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     十一  没有影子
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
艾德
Ed!
娜丁
Nadine?
艾德  我是过来跟你说点事的
Ed, I've come to tell you something.
亲爱的  你的车呢  你怎么过来的
Honey, where's your car? How'd you get here?
-我走过来的  -你走来的
- I walked. - You walked?
你拿着铲子干什么
What's with the shovel?
我正想跟你说这个
That's what I want to talk to you about.
-是吗  -是的
- It is? - Yes.
艾德  我来是想告诉你
Ed, I've come to tell you
我已经变了
I've changed.
是吗
You have?
是的  艾德  你知道我很爱你
Yes, and Ed, you know I love you so much...
我知道  娜丁
I know you do, Nadine.
但我这么多年来一直对你很糟
But I've been a selfish bitch to you all these years,
而你一直都是个圣人
and you've been a saint.
什么
What?
听我说
Listen to me.
我一直都知道你爱诺玛她也爱你
I've known since forever you love Norma and she loves you.
因为我的嫉妒让你们分离
I kept the two of you apart because of my jealousy.
我操纵了你  艾德
And I manipulated you, Ed.
不不  你没有  娜丁
No, no, you haven't, Nadine.
不  你知道这是真的
Oh, no, you know it's true.
我让你觉得愧疚而留在我身边
I guilted you to stay,
而你太好了  真的留了下来
and you're so good you stayed
放弃了自己的爱情
and gave up your love.
天呐  艾德
Oh, god, Ed,
我希望你能自由
I want you to be free.
我现在很好
I'm fine now.
你问拿这把铲子怎么了
You asked about this shovel.
我正把自己从屎里铲出来
Well, I'm shoveling myself out of the shit.
你一直在看雅各比的节目吗
Have you been watching that show of Jacoby's?
那是当然
You know I have.
娜丁...
Nadine...
别担心我了
Don't worry about me.
去找她吧
Run to her.
好好与她相守到老吧
Enjoy the rest of your lives together.
我太开心了
I am so happy
只要一想到你们俩幸福地在一起
Just thinking of you two being happy.
艾德  我爱你  永远都爱
Ed, I love you and always will,
但真爱就是要让对方幸福
but true love is giving the other what makes them happy.
天呐
Jeez,
你这个大块头
you big lug,
太美好了
how beautiful is this!
娜丁  我希望你认真思考下
Nadine, I want you to think real hard about
你刚说的话  因为你不知道自己在说什么
what you're saying because you're not making any sense.
亲爱的  明天你就会希望
Honey, tomorrow, you're gonna wish
你从没说过这些话
you never said these things.
艾德  我说过了
Ed, I told you,
我走了大老远过来
I walked all the way here.
我有足够的时间思考  反悔
I had plenty of time to think, turn back,
但我没有
but I didn't
因为我真的是这么想的
because this is how I really feel.
你可以谢谢安普医生
And you can thank Dr. Amp,
我们的老朋友  雅各比医生
our old friend, Dr. Jacoby.
对我来说  他大概就是这里唯一一个
To me, he's about the only one around here
有一说一的人了
telling it like it is.
所以  就是这样
So, it's just it is.
艾德  你自由了
Ed, you are free.
去享受生活吧
Go and enjoy.
双R餐厅
诺玛  所有事都改变了
Norma, everything has changed.
我刚跟娜丁聊过了
I just spoke with Nadine.
她给了我自由
She's given me my freedom.
艾德  我...
Ed, I'm--
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
沃尔特在这里
Walter's here.
-你收到我的花了吗  -很美...
- Did you get my flowers? - Oh, lovely...
你要点什么  艾德
What can I get you, Ed?
一杯咖啡
Cup of coffee.
马上送上
Coming right up.
还要一片毒药
And a cyanide tablet.
我要你过来一趟
So I asked you to stop by
因为我有事要跟你说
because I have something to tell you.
你决定把餐厅改名为诺玛的双R餐厅了
You're changing the name to Norma's Double R.
我就知道你会改变心意的
I knew you'd come around.
不是的  其实是...
No, actually, um,
我在考虑让你出钱买断我的股份
I'm exercising my option for you to buy me out.
什么
What?
你是在开玩笑吗
Is this a joke?
不是  我是认真的  沃尔特
No, you heard me, Walter.
为什么
But why?
家庭原因
Family reasons.
你不是说你没有家人吗
I thought you told me you didn't have any family?
不  我有一个非常美满的家庭
No, I have a wonderful family.
我想照顾家人
And I want to take care of them.
我太操劳了  总是在操心餐厅的事
I just spread myself too thin, worrying about all these diners.
我想在家庭上多花点时间
I...I want to spend more time at home.
给你
Here you go.
诺玛  我尊重你的决定
Norma, I respect your decision,
尽管我并不是很理解
even if I don't understand it.
我只是很遗憾你将错过
I'm just sorry you're not going to be part
这巨大的成功了
of what is going to be a great success.
我知道会大获成功的
Oh, and I know it will be,
我希望你们一切顺利  沃尔特
and I-I wish you the best of luck, Walter.
但是...
But...
我看了看我的合同
I looked at my contract.
我会按合同保留这家双R
I'm gonna keep the Double R as agreed,
你要买下我其它的分店的股份
and you're gonna buy my shares of the other franchises.
很快就有七家了
Soon to be seven.
七家生意兴隆  宾至如归的餐厅
Seven diners full of happy, satisfied customers.
我有一家就很开心
And I'm happier with just one.
坦白地讲
For the record,
我只想说
I'd just like to say,
你在犯一个大错误
you're making a huge mistake.
我觉得你会后悔的
And I believe you're going to regret it.
嫁给我
Marry me.
当然
Of course I will.
咖啡店
我在找菲利普·杰弗里斯
I'm looking for Phillip Jeffries.
我会帮你开门
是你啊
Oh, it's you.
杰弗里斯
Jeffries.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
为什么你派雷来杀我
Why did you send Ray to kill me?
什么
What?
我打过给雷
I called Ray.
真的是你派他去的
So you did send him?
你五天前打过电话给我吗
Did you call me five days ago?
我没有你的号码
I don't have your number.
所以说别人打给我的吗
So it was someone else who called me?
我们以前常常聊天
We used to talk.
是的
Yes, we did.
现在
Well, now,
我不想聊朱迪
I'm not gonna talk about Judy.
事实上  我们根本不会聊朱迪
In fact, we are not gonna talk about Judy at all.
1989年
1989.
你出现在联调局费城总部
You showed up at FBI headquarters in Philadelphia
说你见过朱迪
and said you'd met Judy.
所以你是库柏吗
So, you are Cooper?
菲利普
Phillip.
你为什么想要聊朱迪
Why didn't you want to talk about Judy?
朱迪是谁
Who is Judy?
朱迪想从我这得到什么吗
Does Judy want something from me?
你何不亲自去问朱迪呢
Why don't you ask Judy yourself?
我帮你写下来吧
Let me write it down for ya.
朱迪是谁
Who is Judy?
你已经见过朱迪了
You've already met Judy.
什么叫我已经见过朱迪
What do you mean, I've met Judy?
朱迪是谁
Who is Judy?
我在农场后院就认出你了
I recognized you back at the farm.
你是联调局探员
You're FBI.
你怎么知道的
How do you figure that?
因为我看过
'Cause I seen your picture
你穿着联调局制服的照片
in your fancy FBI suit.
别再走过来
Don't come any closer.
你在哪看到那些照片的
Where'd you see that picture?
在我妈那里
My mom had it.
谁是你妈
Who's your mom?
奥黛丽·霍恩
Audrey Horne.
你的名字叫库柏
And your name's Cooper.
别再威胁我
Don't ever threaten me again.
上车  我们边开边聊
Get in the truck. We'll talk on the way.
未知号码
拉斯维加斯
为什么
Why?
不可能
There is no why.
是我做的
I did do it.
不
No.
不  是她做的
No, she did it.
是她做的
She did it.
我不行
I can't.
不
No.
是我干的
I did it.
不是的  史蒂文
No. No, steven.
史蒂文  别这样
Steven, stop it.
你什么都没做  明白吗
You didn't do anything, okay?
你当时根本控制不了自己
You were fucking stoned.
她到底给了你个什么东西
What the fuck did she give you?
把枪给我  好不好
Give me the gun, okay?
你要不要跟我一起来
Are you gonna come up with me?
不
No.
不  你也不要走
No, and you're not going either.
看着我
Look at me.
我已经高中毕业了
I'm a high school graduate.
该死...
Oh, fuck...
看见这个了吗
You see this, yeah?
不  不
No. No.
别  别这样
Stop it, don't do that.
我把这个装进去
I'm gonna get this thing in.
什么
What?
不  停下
No--don't, no.
再把这个安上...
I'm gonna put this thing here...
不  不要
No, no.
正对着这里
Right through here.
不
No.
别这样  史蒂文
No, steven.
-别  -这样...
- No. - It's--
这样就能一了百了
It's gonna end it.
不要
No.
等我在上面见到你的时候...
and when I-- when I see you come up...
不过...  不过...
But...But...
我也可能会
I may not even
根本见不到你  我是说...
See you there, I mean...
我是说...
I mean...
我可能已经走了
I mean gone.
我又会去哪里呢
Where will I be?
下辈子变成犀牛吗
Will I be with the rhinoceros?
还是像失忆疑云一样
The lightning in the bottle, hm?
求你了
Please.
没事了  都没事了
It's okay. It's okay, okay.
或者我干脆会
Or will I be completely, uh,
变成像...
Like--like--
石头那样
Turquoise?
好像有什么东西
I feel something.
我操
Fuck.
又或者...
Or...
该死
Fuck.
一切就这么结束了
This is the end.
我还有事要做
I got a duty to do.
你快别待在这里了
Do whatev-- whatever you want.
我很喜欢上你
I liked fucking you.
我跟你说过这个吗
Did I tell you?
真的特别喜欢
I liked it a lot.
和你并肩躺下  纠缠在一起
I liked to get down and fight with you
然后上你
And fuck.
我想让你知道...
Just so you know...
我很喜欢干你的感觉
That I like your cunt.
有时候实在是太美妙了
Like, sometimes, it's so amazing.
你要把我弄哭了
You're making me cry.
别哭了  臭婊子
Stop it, cunt.
我去
Shit.
操  操  操
Fuck. Fuck, fuck.
不
No.
不要
他就住在那边的拖车里
He lives in that trailer right there.
枪炮酒吧
接下来的环节
Next
在公路之家的节目单上
On the roadhouse playlist
是我们的最爱之一
Is one of our favorites.
《盛装打扮》  欢迎尖声
"Sharp dressed man" By zz top.
音量
音量  最大
见到你真好  蕾妮
It's good to see you, Renee.
找死是吧你
You got a death wish?
老子杀了你
Cause I'll fucking kill you.
别跟我老婆说话  休想
Don't talk to my wife. Ever!
我  我只是想说  我想  我在努力地
I wa--I was just saying-- I was try--I was just trying--
想干吗
To--to what?
我只是想礼貌点
I try--I was just trying to be polite.
我  我喜欢她
I-I like her.
停手  查克  别打了
Stop it, Chuck, stop it!
别打了  查克  快停手
别打了  查克
Stop it, Chuck!
你识趣的话就马上停手
You better stop this.
操你妈  废物
Fuck you, punk!
查克  跟我说句话
Chuck, talk to me!
宝贝
Baby!
你还好吗  兄弟
Are you all right, mate?
没事
Yeah.
各位
Hey, anybody,
这些人伤得很重
These guys are really hurt.
快打911
Dial 911 now!
老实说我尽量下手不那么重了  詹姆斯
I tried not to hit them too hard, James, honest.
没事
It's okay.
对了  谢谢你
Thanks, by the way.
我很抱歉  蕾妮
I am so sorry, Renee.
我也没想到会发生这事
I did not mean for this to happen.
真的
I really didn't.
查克  亲爱的  跟我说句话啊
Chuck, baby, talk to me.
天啊
Oh, god.
他的眼睛看上去不大对
His eyes don't look right.
他们到了  警官
Um, they're here, sir,
道格拉斯·琼斯和他妻子  珍
Douglas Jones and his wife, Jane,
准备好接受询问了
ready for questioning.
他有没有给你添什么麻烦
He give you any trouble?
没有  没有
Uh, no, no.
不过孩子们倒不怎么高兴
Um, but the kids aren't too happy.
孩子...们
Kid-s?
还不止一个
Plural?
孩子们
Kid-s?
威尔森
Wilson!
罗杰  进来一下
Roger, get in here a minute.
有什么事吗  警官
Yes, sir?
罗杰  我们有没有收到安东尼的消息
Roger, have we heard from Anthony?
没有  先生
No, sir.
给我去找他
Well, find him for me.
马上去
Now.
亲爱的
Hi, hun.
该死
Oh, shit.
你等一下
Hold on.
嗯  解决一个  还剩一个
Yeah, one down, one to go.
好  薯条
Yeah, french fries.
多加番茄酱
And extra ketchup.
双峰警察局
把他关在八号
Put him in eight.
转身
Back up.
那个戴手套的怪胎干了什么
What'd that gloved freak do now?
闭嘴  查德
Shut up, Chad!
Shut up, Chad.
他在牢里做什么
What's he doing in the cell?
别理他
Don't pay any attention to him.
霍克
Hawk.
他们两个还好吗
Are those guys okay?
都在重症监护
Both in intensive care.
他们都在重症监护
They're both in intensive care.
搞什么
What the hell?
闭嘴
Shut up!
政府也经常这么做
The government does it all the time.
有人收钱做事  就和我们一样
People get paid for it, too, just like us.
说的没错
Damn right.
虚伪的混账
Two-faced fucks.
说什么基督教国家
So-called Christian nation.
还不如说
Might as well be
"汝应杀人"
"Thou shalt kill."
"绝不怜悯"  "拒绝原谅"
"Show no mercy." "Forgive no one."
去他们的
Fuck 'em in the ass.
这是杀人凶手的国度  到处杀人
It's a nation of killers, killing all along.
几乎屠杀了所有的印第安人  可不是吗
Killed damn near all the Indians, didn't they?
是啊
Yeah.
但是我杀了人之后乐趣就结束了
But my fun's over when we actually kill someone.
虐待尸体没意思
It's no fun torturing a corpse.
我已经几百年
I haven't got to torture anybody
没有虐待人了  哈齐
in a fuck of a long time, Hutch.
我知道
I know.
只是最近都没什么机会
Just hadn't worked out lately.
我操
It's fucked.
你知道我讨厌
You know I hate it
你拿这些小包番茄酱给我
when you get me these little ketchup packs.
对不起  他们只有这些
I'm sorry. It's all they had.
你有帮我带甜点吗
Did you get me dessert?
当然有
You know I did.
我爱你  哈齐
I love you, Hutch.
我爱你  香塔尔
I love you, Chantal.
今夜真美
Beautiful night.
火星
Mars.
这给你  道吉
Here you go, Dougie.
好不好吃
Is it delicious?
好吃
Delicious.
道吉
Oh, Dougie.
感觉我们的梦想都要成真了
It's like all our dreams are coming true.
真了
True.
再见  诺玛
Good-bye, Norma.
看看他们能做些什么
We'll see what they can do.
我不担心  一切都会没事的
I'm not worried. Everything will be fine.
原班人马再次集结
The old team together again.
没什么能阻止我们
Nothing can stop us.
原班人马  没错
The old team. Yeah.
-再见  亲爱的  -再见  德米尔先生
- Good-bye, dear. - Good-bye, Mr. Demille.
怎么样
How'd it go?
进展得非常顺利
It couldn't have gone better.
基本都好了
It's practically set.
他得先完成这幅画
Good he has to finish this picture first.
我的就是下一个
Mine will be his next.
去找戈登·科尔
Get Gordon Cole.
告诉他别管我们的车了
Tell him to forget about our car.
告诉他可以随便再搞一辆旧车
Tell him he can get another old car someplace--
妈妈  怎么回事
Mom, what was that?
霍克副局长  霍克副局长
Deputy Hawk? Deputy Hawk?
玛格丽特·兰特曼一号线呼叫
Margaret Lanterman's on line one.
好的  露西
Okay, Lucy.
玛格丽特  有什么事吗
Margaret, what can I do for ya?
霍克
Hawk.
我快死了
I'm dying.
我很遗憾  玛格丽特
I'm sorry, Margaret.
你了解死亡
You know about death,
这只是一种变数
That it's just a change,
不是终结
not an end.
霍克
Hawk.
时间到了
It's time.
还是有些恐惧
There's some fear,
恐惧这么放下
some fear in letting go.
记得我跟你说过的话
Remember what I told you.
我在电话里不能再多说了
I can't say more over the phone.
但你知道我的意思
But you know what I mean,
从我们的谈话
from our talks,
我们之前能面对面交流的时候
when we were able to speak face to face.
小心那个
Watch for that one,
那个我和你说过的
the one I told you about,
月光下
the one under the moon
蓝色松林山上的那个
on blue pine mountain.
霍克
Hawk.
我的木头变成金色了
My log is turning gold.
风在呼啸
The wind is moaning.
我要死了
I'm dying.
晚安  霍克
Good night, Hawk.
晚安  玛格丽特
Good night, Margaret.
再见  玛格丽特
Good-bye, Margaret.
出什么事了
What's up?
霍克找我们的
Hawk intercommed us,
要我们来这里见他
told us to meet him here.
玛格丽特·兰特曼今晚去世了
Margaret Lanterman passed away tonight.
木头女士死了
The log lady's dead?
我不想再等电话了
I'm just tired of waiting for the phone.
比利讨厌那个地方  但是...
Billy hated that place, but...
你穿上了你的外套
Oh. You got your coat on.
当然了
Of course I do.
我们要出去
We're going out.
我们要去酒馆
We're going to the roadhouse.
我需要我的外套
I will need my coat.
是啊  我...
Yeah, well, yeah, I just...
你可真麻烦  查理
You're really something, Charlie.
搞什么
What the hell?
穿上你的外套  奥黛丽
Put your coat on, Audrey.
已经很晚了  我很困
It's already late and I'm so sleepy.
我们走
Let's go.
你能别抱怨了吗
Would you just stop complaining?
天啊  你真是烦人
God, what a pain in the ass you are.
你就不能闭上你的嘴巴
I mean, can't you just do something for someone else
帮别人做事的时候别满腹怨言吗
without ruining it by continually complaining?
你真是爱抱怨  就像一只有病的小狗
You're such a whiner, it's like being with a sick dog.
你要穿上外套
Are you gonna put your coat on
还是要这样把我烦死
or talk me to death right here, on the threshold?
比利和我出门的时候
You know, when Billy and I go places,
从来不会像你这样和我说话  查理
he never speaks to me the way you do, Charlie.
没错
Yes.
我是查理
Well, I am Charlie
他是比利
and he is Billy.
我更喜欢比利
And I like Billy better.
太感性了
Sensational.
你要不要穿上外套
Now, are you gonna put your coat on
还是说我们要在这里站一整晚
or shall we stand here all night?
又来了
Here you go again.
你就不能消停一会
You can't stop for one fucking second.
奥黛丽  说真的
Audrey, seriously,
再拖一秒  我就要脱掉外套
in one fucking second, I'm taking my coat off
今晚不出去了
and staying in for the night.
想去酒馆的是你
You're the one that wanted to go to the roadhouse,
不是我
Not me.
真是不可能
It's impossible.
就这样在我眼前
I mean, I see it right before my eyes,
但我以前竟然都没发现
but I never really saw it before.
真是太不可能了
It's absolutely fucking impossible.
又怎么了  奥黛丽
What is it now, Audrey?
你  查理  是你
You, Charlie, it's you.
我以前从来没发现
I-I-I just never really saw you before
你是这样的人
the way I'm seeing you now.
好像变得完全不一样了
Like I'm meeting a different person.
你是谁  查理
Who are you, Charlie?
好吧  脱掉外套
Okay, off comes the coat.
你怎么能这样
How can you be like this?
我恨你这个混蛋
I hate your fucking guts!
我恨你
I hate you!
你知道我有多恨你吗
Do you know how much I fucking hate you?
枪炮酒吧
我在等人
I'm waiting for someone.